question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan &quot;We hire mercenaries and get in fights&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&quot; series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A flock of crows is known as a homicide.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "3 members of 2 Live Crew were arrested for playing songs from their album, As Nasty As They Wanna Be, live.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Killer Whale is considered a type of dolphin.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
